http://www.opensourcecms.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyEffective date: April 30, 2018GFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://www.opensourcecms.com website (the “Service”).This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.opensourcecms.comContents1 Definitions1.1 Personal Data1.2 Usage Data1.3 Cookies1.4 Data Controller1.5 Data Processor (or Service Providers)1.6 Data Subject1.7 User2 Information Collection And Use2.1 Types of Data Collected2.1.1 Personal Data2.1.2 Usage Data2.1.3 Tracking & Cookies Data3 Use of Data4 Retention of Data5 Transfer Of Data6 Disclosure Of Data6.1 Disclosure for Law Enforcement6.2 Legal Requirements7 Security Of Data8 “Do Not Track” Signals9 Your Rights10 Service Providers10.1 Analytics10.2 Advertising11 Links To Other Sites12 Children’s Privacy13 Changes To This Privacy Policy14 Contact UsDefinitionsPersonal DataPersonal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).Usage DataUsage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).CookiesCookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.Data ControllerData Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.Data Processor (or Service Providers)Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller.We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.Data SubjectData Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.UserThe User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.Information Collection And UseWe collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.Types of Data CollectedPersonal DataWhile using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:Email addressFirst name and last nameCookies and Usage DataWe may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.Usage DataWe may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.Tracking & Cookies DataWe use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.Examples of Cookies we use:Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.Advertising Cookies. Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.Use of DataGFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH uses the collected data for various purposes:To provide and maintain our ServiceTo notify you about changes to our ServiceTo allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do soTo provide customer supportTo gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our ServiceTo monitor the usage of our ServiceTo detect, prevent and address technical issuesTo provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such informationRetention of DataGFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.GFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.Transfer Of DataYour information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.If you are located outside Germany and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Germany and process it there.Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.GFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.Disclosure Of DataDisclosure for Law EnforcementUnder certain circumstances, GFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).Legal RequirementsGFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:To comply with a legal obligationTo protect and defend the rights or property of GFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbHTo prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the ServiceTo protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the publicTo protect against legal liabilitySecurity Of DataThe security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.“Do Not Track” SignalsWe do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.Your RightsGFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.In certain circumstances, you have the right:To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about youTo rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurateTo request the deletion of Personal Data held about youYou have the right to data portability for the information you provide to GFDK Gesellschaft für digitale Kaufberatung mbH. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.Service ProvidersWe may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.AnalyticsWe may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.Google Analytics: Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/Addthis: Addthis is a social media sharing and web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Addthis uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Addthis services. Addthis may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.You can opt-out by using the button on the Addthis web page http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-outAdvertisingWe may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Service.Google AdSense & DoubleClick Cookie: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet.You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/Links To Other SitesOur Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.Changes To This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:By visiting this page on our website: https://www.opensourcecms.com/imprint/
(38 votes, average: 3.92 out of 5)Privacy Policy 3.92 5 38 Loading...
Do you want to advertise on this site?Contact usCMS CategoriesBlog (28)Clan CMS (4)CMF (1)CMS / Portals (342)CRM (1)ECM (1)eCommerce (21)Forum (15)Groupware (7)Image Galleries (8)Lite / Simple (11)LMS / LCMS (5)MVC (2)Social Dating (1)WAF (1)Wiki (4)Popular DemosWordPress DemoDrupal DemoMODx DemoTypo3 DemoJoomla Democoncrete5 DemoNew Demos webEdition Cuppa CMS H.H.G. multistore Shopware LaravelMagazine ArchivePopular topicsCMS Market ShareHow to Choose a CMSCMS vs. FrameworksFree Website HostingBest WordPress SEO PluginsShow all topics >>BlogrollOur MissionOpenSourceCMS.com is a central resource for all things related to Open Source CMS and gives you the opportunity to “try out” most of the best Open Source CMS tools in the world without marketing fluff or sales people.FeaturedAbout UsOpen-Source MagazineCMS Market ShareOpen-Source versus Closed Source CMSWeb Hosting ComparisonAbout UsSubmit Your CMSContactImage CreditsPrivacy PolicyImprint
